# Sample json output from the view
# My apologize for the lack of tabs
[
{
"field_question_number": "1",
"field_question": "What is the purpose of the System Development Life Cycle?",
"field_answer": [
"To build and maintain organizations",
"To build and maintain computer a based information system",
"To organize documents online",
"To create an information technology framework for e-commerce"
],
"field_correct": "2",
"title": "1 purpose of SDLC"
},
{
"field_question_number": "2",
"field_question": "Modularizing is the process of breaking down a program into modules?",
"field_answer": [
"True",
"False"
],
"field_correct": "1",
"title": "2 Modularizing"
},
{
"field_question_number": "3",
"field_question": "Object Oriented Programming allows:",
"field_answer": [
"The ability to write programs with the assembly language",
" Programs to be modularized into objects or classes",
"Tiny programs that are used only in a GUI environment",
"The grouping of simple programs into one structured one"
],
"field_correct": "2",
"title": "3 OOP Allows"
},
{
"field_question_number": "4",
"field_question": "What are the two main program design tools?",
"field_answer": [
"CASE and System flow chart",
"Structure Chart and Hierarchy chart",
"Pseudo-code and System flow chart",
"Pseudo-code and Program Flow Chart"
],
"field_correct": "4",
"title": "4 2 Main Program Design Tools"
},
{
"field_question_number": "5",
"field_question": "The System flow chart is",
"field_answer": [
"A graphical representation of the programs within a system and its data flow",
"A graphical representation of the hardware architecture",
"A diagram that shows the faults with a system",
"None of the above"
],
"field_correct": "1",
"title": "5 System Flow Chart"
},
{
"field_question_number": "6",
"field_question": "The person responsible for analyzing the system is the",
"field_answer": [
"Systems Administrator",
"Programmer",
"System Designer",
"System Analyst"
],
"field_correct": "4",
"title": "6 Analyzing the System"
},
{
"field_question_number": "7",
"field_question": "A computer-based information system is a",
"field_answer": [
"System comprised of PDA, Laptops and Desktops",
"System in which some procedures are performed by computers",
"Inventory Management is performed",
"A type of payroll system"
],
"field_correct": "2",
"title": "7 CBI is"
},
{
"field_question_number": "8",
"field_question": "CASE tools allows",
"field_answer": [
"Software to be tested online",
"Software to be easily distributed among a developer community",
"The rapid increase in the development of software due to extensive design approach",
"The bypassing of alot of logical code"
],
"field_correct": "3",
"title": "8 CASE"
},
{
"field_question_number": "9",
"field_question": "The Program Development Cycle is",
"field_answer": [
"A language built by a programmer",
"A cycle similar to SDLC",
"A Cycle that creates a programmed logical output",
"A series of steps taken for the development of a program"
],
"field_correct": "4",
"title": "9 Program Dev Cycle"
},
{
"field_question_number": "10",
"field_question": "A Programming Language named FORTRAN is good for",
"field_answer": [
"Handling character sets",
"Numerical data",
"Shell commands",
"None of the above"
],
"field_correct": "2",
"title": "10 FORTRAN"
}
]
